advanced-ip-scanner.com 2016-06-08

# Advanced IP Scanner - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Famatech’s website located at [www.advanced-ip-scanner.com](http://www.advanced-ip-scanner.com/). We are firmly committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we are pleased to provide this Privacy Policy to describe our information gathering and use.

#### Acquisition of information

You may visit our site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Our site does collect information such as domain, IP address, browser type and operating system for site trends and statistics, but this information does not personally identify you.

#### How we use the information

The personal information you provide will be used for the purpose for which it was provided - to contact you, to process an order, to register your product, etc. Famatech may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to provide customer support to you. Famatech may also use your contact information to provide notices regarding the products, as well as to inform you about new products or promotional campaigns.

#### Information Security

Famatech will strictly protect the security of your personal information, protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Your personal data, including your e-mail address, is used for internal purposes only and is never sold or shared with anyone outside of Famatech, unless we disclose information in response to a law enforcement request.

Copyright © 1999-2016 Famatech.  
All rights reserved.
